We'll bring back what we learned
to Travis Japan.
We'll embark on many, many more
spectacular journeys together. Agreed?
[all] Agreed!
-[cheering, in English] Let's go, TJ!
-Let's go!
Let's go!
[in Japanese] Thank you!
Couldn't have asked for better band mates.
You're the best!
[narrator] It's the special summer break
Noel organized
for the Travis Japan members.
After traveling through
the southwestern United States,
the Travis Japan members
arrived in Sedona.
The seven friends enjoyed
a heartfelt reunion.
[♪ opening theme music plays]
Travis Japan
SUMMER VACATION!! IN THE USA
Sedona, Arizona.
[Noel, in Japanese]
No matter how many years pass,
Travis Japan will never forget this place.
I've got two great spots in mind.
-Yeah?
-Really, now.
I really wanted a group photo
that includes all seven of us
with Sedona in the background.
-Nice.
-Great. Nice idea.
Let's go with that.
Let's make our way to
the photo shoot location. Yeah?
I'm down. Let's get moving.
It's been ages since the seven of us
walked together like this.
That's true.
-We didn't walk at all yesterday.
-Nope, we sat around on our butts.
We had a scrumptious meal though.
-Man, did we eat.
-You know it.
-Ain't that the truth.
-That's all right.
-Travis Japan is always moving forward.
-[band members exclaim]
-Cringe.
-Say what?
-You callin' him cringe?
-[Machu] Zuya-nii!
-The sunlight through the leaves is nice.
-What a nice hidden spot.
This is it, the real Sedona.
Let's go, Sedona!
Sedona's just like Ikspiari,
the gateway to Tokyo Disneyland.
-[band members, in English] Hi! Hello!
-[tourists] Hi!
-Hello! Hello!
-[tourists] Hello, how are you?
[in Japanese] Is this the right way?
Wanna switch spots?
-'Preciate it.
-No prob.
-How's the setup, Shime?
-Want me to take over?
No, stay there.
What did we switch spots for?
-Lookin' good.
-Press the timer.
[Shime] Okay. Here we go.
-There isn't a countdown. Get ready, guys.
-It's going!
Now, dash.
This'll be a photo we cherish.
Right, let's give off a heartwarming vibe.
-How did it turn out?
-It's great. It turned out super.
-We're lookin' good.
-We're killing it.
-It's rad.
-Isn't it a good one?
You got the money shot.
-Simply put, we killed it.
-Yep.
-Hey. Kura. Take a look.
-You're right.
Wowza! [laughing]
Machu's high up!
-We lifted him up so high.
-We got a killer shot.
We have three to choose from.
-I love that we shot a few different ones.
-What a great view too.
-How nice.
-We've got another one for the books.
We captured the Sedona vibe.
-I hope this photo will reach many people.
-Sedona is a picturesque little place.
Right on.
[narrator, in Japanese] Sedona, Arizona.
There is a place known
for its spiritual energy.
Many visitors recount the otherworldly
feeling they get when they're here.
Take one step onto the red soil here,
and you'll be met with pure serenity.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
-It's all connected?
-It is. It's all connected.
Noel and Machu wanted to visit
this spiritual hot spot
before departing Sedona.
The duo split up from the rest of
the members to enjoy a morning hike.
-It's way too early.
-[laughing] Yep.
We're two early risers.
-It's 7:00 a.m. sharp.
-Yes. But we've got a clear, blue sky.
-We sure do.
-Not a cloud in sight.
Yeah. The sky stretches endlessly.
Yep. We're hiking up there.
-[Machu] That huge rock?
-Can you believe it?
-That rock formation's our destination.
-How close are we getting to it?
[Noel] Who knows? Better get started.
[Machu] We're comin' for you!
Meanwhile, the other five…
-We've made it to Slide Rock!
-[all cheer] Here we are!
We're gettin' wet!
Machu and Noel left for their hike early.
-And we chose the river.
-They went on a hike?
That's right.
-Hey, knock it off! Seriously!
-Yo.
It's freezing! Watch out for the camera!
Camera?
-You got this on camera?
-We're here to have a blast!
[Shizu] I'm done with your antics!
-Watch it! It's chilly!
-Let's have some fun.
[Machu] This is amazing.
Seriously, it's the great outdoors.
We're trekking through
the real-life Big Thunder Mountain.
[Noel] No joke.
-Wait, did you hear?
-[Machu] What?
[Noel] Sedona was the inspiration
for Big Thunder Mountain.
-No kidding!
-That's right.
Walt Disney based the ride on the town
after visiting himself.
[Machu] No kidding. And we're at
the very place Walt Disney came.
[Noel] Yes, consider it
a pilgrimage of sorts.
Geez, well I feel honored.
We're honored to follow
in Walt Disney's footsteps.
[Machu] You spent the entire week
neck-deep in taco-making?
It was a tacolicious week,
I tell you what.
-Those tacos were the bomb. Seriously.
-Then it was worthwhile.
You'd think I'm exaggerating,
but those tacos were life-changing.
So when we order catering
for our live shows,
can we request tacos from you?
-Easily.
-That's the best.
[Noel] I prefer to be on the stage though.
-[Machu] Do both.
-[both laugh]
Perform on stage and cater the food.
I'll do both.
[Machu] This view is phenomenal.
I keep repeating myself, but it really is
like a real-life Big Thunder Mountain.
[Noel laughs] Agreed.
[exclaims]
You got me!
-He's done it now.
-Stop it! No, no!
Seriously, I'll end up hurt!
-Don't mess with me. Hands off!
-Get 'em, get 'em.
-Shoot, shoot! I'm not joking anymore!
-Play nice.
[screams]
Time to scram.
I hurt my knee!
[Genta] I'm callin' truce!
Stop it, you jerks!
You better not do this! Hey!
You Team A's full of…
-Hey!
-I'm not going down!
Never!
[laughing]
It's freezing! I'ma get hypothermia!
Wait, wait! Stop!
[screams, shrieks]
It's freezing! It's punishingly cold!
[Noel] Did you interact with many locals?
[Machu] I sure did.
I made a hat with a nice hatmaker
and stuff.
[Noel] Okay, okay.
[Machu] We also spoke
to a bunch of shopkeepers.
[Noel] Of course you did.
It's not every day
you're immersed in live English.
[Machu] It's true.
[Noel] And this region, so New Mexico,
Arizona, and the Southwest at large,
has a large Hispanic population.
We're both trying to communicate
using imperfect English.
[Machu] I know what you mean.
I love the heartfelt communication
we get out of it.
Yes. We understand each other.
Exactly.
What a fantastic view.
I love it.
-Good work making it this far.
-Likewise.
-We've got a long way to go. [chuckles]
-[laughs]
-We won't be done anytime soon.
-No kidding.
-Hold on.
-My goodness, this view is to die for.
What a magnificent view.
Only in Sedona.
Only in Sedona indeed.
These reds and greens
are so iconic to Sedona.
Hup.
Incredible.
[sighs] What a nice breeze.
It doesn't feel real.
No, it doesn't.
-Shall we keep going?
-We shall.
Where's the goal?
[tourist] Wow!
They said, "Wow." I feel them.
Same.
Hup.
Wow.
-It already looks breathtaking.
-Isn't this something?
Just wow.
-[Umi] Oh, Shime.
-[Shizu] Shime.
Didn't think we'd spare only you,
now, did you?
-Leave it, we've got a change of clothes.
-I'll take you on.
Crap, he means business.
We were surrounded by nature
this entire trip.
I've become quite comfortable around it.
Not too long ago,
I would've hated jumping in the water.
What was your trip like?
We visited all sorts of towns…
-Right, right.
-…and learned their history.
They told us about the history
behind turquoise jewelry,
-how they're made and such.
-I see.
We also learned the role turquoise plays
in the Native American culture,
-and the significance of wearing it.
-I see, I see.
We got a deep look into their culture.
-How wonderful.
-It really was.
-So, we were chatting yesterday.
-Right, right.
And we all agreed you were
into this trip the most.
-[laughing] Really?
-None of us expected that.
-You talked about me?
-We did.
You're a homebody
-who loves to play video games.
-Right.
It's what I like to do.
So we didn't know
if you were enjoying this trip.
Right, right, right.
But yesterday at the dinner,
we all felt you got the most out of it.
I had a blast. It was such a great trip.
I visited many sites.
Really, every bit of it was fun.
I'm even having fun hanging out here.
It's been a while since
I last took a dip in a river…
Right, right.
…and I'm thinking, "This is unbeatable."
[Shime exclaims]
[screams]
-Got 'em! [laughing]
-It's freezing!
Haven't heard you that loud in a while.
Wait, are we supposed to climb up here?
-No way.
-It's ridiculously steep.
-What a rough trail. Hold on, hold on.
-I need a minute.
-[Noel] It's such a steep trail.
-[Machu] I can't believe it.
It's too soon to check out
the view behind us.
-You're right. Good insight.
-I'll wait on it.
-"Too soon to look back."
-[Machu chuckles]
-That's my quote of the day.
-[Noel] There it is.
[grunts]
-[Noel] Incredible! I can't believe this.
-It's unbelievable.
It really is.
-It's more of a cliff than a trail.
-[Machu] We're scaling a wall.
[both grunting]
Hup.
-[Noel] Seriously, this…
-[Machu] Hup-ho.
Scaling the Cathedral Rock in one go,
no stops in between,
it's just as exciting as being on stage.
I honestly feel that.
-Do you know which part of the cactus…
-Yeah?
…is the leaves?
-Not these parts?
-[chuckles]
That's what you'd think, right?
It's actually the needles.
[Machu] What? I would've never guessed.
[Noel] Isn't it intriguing?
To start, I had no idea
a cactus was shaped like this.
[Noel laughs]
[Machu] I thought,
"Aren't they supposed to be round?"
[Noel] Most people imagine succulents
when they hear cactus.
Is that why?
My goodness!
[Noel] Hold on.
TJ!
[Machu laughing] It's echoey.
Travis Japan!
[laughing]
[Machu shrieks, laughs]
[Noel] I hear a dog.
Guess there's a feral dog somewhere.
Look, it says "End of Trail."
-We made it!
-At last!
-We actually did it!
-[cheers]
This is surreal.
You'd never understand this feeling
unless you hike up here yourself.
-Yeah.
-This overwhelming feeling.
[Noel] It's like Chaka said yesterday.
We can share a photo of this place…
Yes.
…but you have to see this in person
to understand.
-It's indescribable.
-Exactly.
This is amazing. It's all real.
It's deeply moving.
I know I said I won't look behind me
til I reach the top, but…
Right.
-The best view was in front of me.
-[chuckles]
What an incredible view.
You said this place is
a spiritual hot spot, right?
Right.
-Shall we feel the spiritual energy here?
-Let's do it.
[Noel exclaims]
[Noel] This is incredible!
Talk about a precipice.
-[chuckles]
-Wow.
I'm getting chills.
[♪ serene pipe music playing]
-[♪ music continues]
-[no audible dialogue]
-Whoo!
-Let's go!
-Comin'!
-Time to hit the road.
-Let's go.
-Let's go, let's go.
-Let's get going.
Time to get outta here.
-We've got our own car.
-Hop in, guys.
-What a big car.
-[in English] Thank you.
[in Japanese] All right.
Time to hit the road.
Let's get goin'!
Hup.
I'll take this seat.
[Noel] Been a while since
we've last been in a car together.
So it has.
Heck yes. Noel's takin' the wheel.
-Yeah!
-It's been a while.
-A bit cramped in here.
-I'll scoot up.
Here we go.
-Let's go, let's go! Time for a road trip!
-We're counting on you, Noel!
[all cheering]
[♪ blues music playing]
[Machu] So it begins.
[Genta] Finally, all seven of us
in a car together.
-Right?
-It's been a while.
-Me, I'm content…
-Right?
…just spending time with you guys.
But you aren't in your usual seats.
-Nice observation.
-True that.
-[Noel] My nerves are kicking in.
-[laughs]
[Noel] I looked forward to this
for the past week.
The seven of us have finally hit the road.
Our next destination is a city close
to Travis Japan's heart, Los Angeles.
[in English] Sixty-six.
[in Japanese] Route 66.
I wonder if Route 66
has historical significance?
During the Gold Rush, laborers traveled
on this route to reach the west coast,
hoping to strike gold or find jobs.
From east to west.
[Noel] Right. It was a road of dreams.
Interesting.
Which means, originally,
it wasn't maintained this well.
[Noel] That's right.
It must've gotten paved over time.
[Shime] I see.
And now, we, the aspiring musicians,
are traveling this very road of dreams.
-It gives me chills.
-That's deep!
-You're a poet today.
-That hit me right in the feels.
[narrator] Seligman, Arizona.
This legendary town breathed new life
into the Mother Road.
On this main street
where time stands still,
traces of the American dream linger.
-[laughs]
-That's a cute photo spot.
What do you think about that stand-in?
Let's poke our heads out of it.
What? I wanna do it.
What? Let's go, let's go!
Let's snap a photo. Let's do it!
Right there.
-I love it! Cute.
-You guys look cute.
You look great.
[Umi] You guys are synced up!
Best buddies.
-You're lookin' great!
-Thanks.
-Here, here.
-Thank you.
Next, next.
-Do you want a photo, Umi?
-Move along, guys.
-Hey, someone…
-Hurry, get in the spot.
Shizuya's…
Wait, he needs a buddy!
Shizuya's by himself.
-He needs a buddy.
-What about Chaka?
[Umi] He went somewhere.
[Shime] Say cheese.
Snappity-snap.
-Lookin' cute.
-You look great.
-Nice!
-Thanks.
Thanks, guys!
[♪ country blues music playing]
[narrator] This town's glory days
ended with the gold mine.
Now, it's a popular tourist spot
where wild burros roam.
It's a lively town where one can
step into the world of Old Westerns.
-I saw burros. Did you?
-There are a ton of burros here.
Well… They're wild.
Best to steer clear of them.
-Back in the day…
-Do you think they'd kick?
…laborers used burros to transport oil.
-[Noel] That's why they're still around.
-[Shizu] Yep.
-And now, they roam freely?
-That's a perfect two shot.
I believe so.
-Cute.
-How cute.
-What a friendly burro.
-It's docile.
See ya, buddy.
[burro brays]
[narrator] The ancestors of these friendly
burros once worked alongside miners.
In the present day, these friendly
creatures are the stars of this town.
[Shime] Wait, wait, wait, wait…
-You'll get some, all right?
-[Noel] How cute! This little…
Can I pet you?
-[Umi] You made a new friend.
-[Shime] Right?
To reward horses, you pat them right here
and say, "Good job."
Really?
Good job.
-I did it all the time in my school club.
-Good job.
Right?
-Were you in the equestrian club?
-I was in the equestrian club.
Right?
It must be where Noel learned
to "horse around."
-The horses taught him.
-No, no.
-They fought.
-I'm all out.
Let's get going. Let's move on.
-Here.
-Okay?
I told you, I don't have anymore.
See? No more.
[Umi] Thanks for playing with us.
-Okay, last little bit.
-That's the very last one. Just for you.
Please. No more. Now, go away.
-They gave him a shake down.
-I mean it. I'm all emptied out.
[Shime] I'll leave this here, all right?
Sorry.
I was startled.
-I thought it was Genta. Nope.
-Hey, everyone!
I tossed some out
so they'd stop chasing me.
They came at me since
I was close to Machu.
This was a great little stop. Bye-bye!
-Right this way, please.
-'Til next time!
-Are we grabbing food?
-Yeah.
Sorry, not here.
Is this a restaurant?
That's what it says here.
There are too many establishments.
Here we go. This is it. Finally!
[narrator] This is the Oatman Hotel.
It's a historic hotel where many
Old Western stars and celebrities stayed.
The nights the stars spent here
still live on in this hotel.
Each dollar bill plastered on the walls
tells a tale of the travelers' dreams.
Here, time and money alike
turn into memories.
-Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-[Noel] What? How fascinating.
What the heck?
Holy smokes.
[♪ gospel song playing]
Are these all bills?
Just what is this about?
The bills are plastered
up and down the wall.
It's incredible.
Thousands of dollars cover the walls!
-These are all dollar bills.
-I'll have Wild West Buffalo Wings.
-[in English] Wings?
-Yes.
-Excuse me?
So, why so many dollars in here?
-How many? Why are there so many dollars?
-Yeah.
So, when the miners were here
mining for gold,
they would get paid
and they didn't wanna take the money
out to the mines,
'cause they would lose it
or not make it back.
So, they'd write their name on it,
stick it to the walls
so they could pay for a haircut,
bar tab, hotel room,
and that's how it originally started
back in the '30s and '40s.
Um, and there's close to
half a million dollars here.
-Half a million?
-Half a million? Wow.
-[Noel] Really? Half a million?
-Yep. Yep.
It's on top, and top,
and top of each other.
Is it kind of…
-Uh, so many bills for… Is kind of…
-[server] Yes.
For, like, to pay for a haircut.
-A haircut?
-Everything back then was five cents.
-So, one dollar, you had all the change.
-Really?
-So, it's kind of like a bank.
-A bank…
-Okay. Okay.
-Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
So, do we need to steal the…
our bills for here with our--
The last person that stole,
they got shot
and they're buried in the back,
so you better be careful.
[Noel] Okay. Got it.
-Thank you. Sorry. Thank you.
-Yeah.
[in Japanese] All right, mining means
"to dig for precious ores."
These bills belonged to the miners
who flocked here during the Gold Rush
-hoping to strike gold.
-[Shizu] That tracks.
-That's why, the money…
-Yes.
-First time eating it deep-fried.
-That's right.
-This is delicious.
-It hits the spot.
[Shizu] We've got a following of flies.
[Genta] It's good to have a following,
even if they're flies.
[Shizu] It's important.
-[in English] We have already three, so…
-Thank you.
Thank you.
[Shime] Miner Burger.
-[in Japanese] Here, use this.
-Thank you.
[Noel] Miner means "someone who mines."
Maybe there's history behind
this burger too.
[Shime] I see.
-[in English] Hot wings.
-Wow.
-Hot Buffalo Wings.
-Hot wings here.
-Okay. Crispy chicken salad.
-Doesn't it look tasty?
-Crispy, please.
-Yep.
-There you go.
-Doesn't it?
Buffalo burger, onion rings,
American cheese.
-American cheese.
Here you go.
-[in Japanese] That's good.
-Time to dig in.
-Diggin' in!
-Digging in!
Awesome.
This is the best.
Yum.
It's supreme.
Delicious.
-It's very good.
-Yum.
-My tummy is rejoicing.
-So good.
This is bliss.
[Shizu] The veggies are good too.
-It's friggin' good.
-Thanks for finding a great spot.
-No prob.
-This is so good.
-Thanks.
-Right? Isn't it delicious?
-I happened to come across it.
-[Genta exclaiming] Mmm!
So yummy.
Let's order this food
for rehearsal breaks.
-Nice.
-Wanna order some?
We can't.
The buns are the best part.
They're crispy.
-Indeed, they are crispy and delicious.
-You copied me.
Yeah, these buns hit the spot!
Love their crispy texture.
That's the fourth time.
It's getting a bit spicy.
[Noel] Is the buffalo burger gamy?
[Umi] Buffalo? Not at all.
It's the same as a classic burger.
-Actually?
-There's nothing to it, really.
It's no different from a classic burger.
It's about as basic a burger
as you can get.
American units confuse me.
-They confuse me too.
-No kidding.
There are ounces and gallons,
and one gallon equals 3.8 liters.
Oh, and 12 ounces make up a gallon.
Okay, I'm completely lost.
-[Machu] Fahrenheit is a mystery to me.
-I'm on the same boat.
-It is a different ball game.
-For temperature…
For temperature, take Celsius,
multiply it by 9/5th,
then add 32 to convert it to Fahrenheit.
A toddler could solve that.
-You caught all that?
-So…
Let's say the temp on the AC is set to 70.
What is that in Celsius?
Subtract 32 from 70, then you get 38.
You take 5/9th of 38, which equals…
Seven, five… It's about…
-Well?
-Twenty…
-About twenty-two, three degrees Celsius?
-Twenty… I see. Maybe? That tracks.
-Sounds about right.
-We just need to know the approximate.
-The approximate's all we wanna know.
-Noel's equation is all we need.
So 70 is about 22.
I usually set the AC to 73.
-Me too.
-Same.
-Seventy's a bit chilly.
-A bit, yeah.
-Seventy's chilly.
-And 60 is sweater weather.
-Sixty's pretty chilly.
-Yeah.
Seventy-three's the best temperature
to wake up to.
[Noel]
Is Machu gonna drive the second leg?
-Wait, I am?
-I'm only saying. If you can't…
-[Machu] We need a plan.
-[Noel] What should we do?
-Yeah, really though.
-I don't mind.
-Shall we hit the road?
-We already are!
Oh, we're already on the way!
Thanks, Machu!
Let's go!
I don't drive on these roads often.
-Alongside the burros.
-Burros, everywhere.
I'd get freaked out if one of them
jumped in front of the car.
-[Umi] Be confident.
-Burros don't cross the street in Japan.
[Machu] Hello, friend.
[Shime] Animals don't jump
in front of cars in Japan, do they?
-[Shizu] Don't think so.
-Hello, there.
Wait, hold on!
-Get outta the way!
-Go right!
-Wanna turn to the right?
-Let's do it.
-Let's go.
-Watch the one to the right.
-What about behind the car?
-We're good.
Watch out! That was close.
-Make up your mind, burro!
-Another one incoming to the right.
Oh, what?
Hey now!
-Oh, come on.
-We don't have treats for you!
We don't have any more!
What's this, a safari park?
-We're outta stock!
-This is too funny.
They got us.
-Just give up.
-Leave it to me.
-I'll get them outta our way.
-Wait!
-This might work.
-He looks like he's got treats for them.
-Wait, how…
-Whoa, whoa!
It ran off!
What?
Here they come…
Watch out. Coming up behind you, Genta.
Genta, wait… wait, wait, wait.
Genta, behind you!
Just pull over.
Hold on, he left the door open.
-Let's take a picture.
-Wait. Oh no, Genta!
-This burro's trying to come in!
-The door's wide open!
-Oh no! It wants to come inside! Crap!
-Close the door, hurry!
-Go ahead, full speed.
-Slam it shut!
-Now, go! Pedal to the metal!
-Thanks.
-Go left.
-You'll be missed, Genta.
It's fine, they're not in the way.
You won't crash into them.
-Shall we say our farewell to Genta?
-Let's say bye to Genta.
-Oh no…
-Anything behind us?
-You're good.
-You're in the lane.
Let's go. We're good, we're good.
[chuckling]
-Nice going!
-Thank you.
-Great job, Genta.
-How was my dance?
You busted out your dance moves.
Don't forget to buckle up.
Now the burros are galloping!
-What's up with them?
-Machu, we're surrounded!
Machu, can we take the left lane instead?
-We're good.
-Are there cars coming?
I know what it is.
It's time for burros to go home.
-Is it their curfew?
-Nice.
-These burros have a curfew.
-They have a curfew.
-That's why they're in a hurry.
-That explains it.
-This isn't normal.
-Things are gettin' desperate.
-Right?
-I never expected this to happen.
[Shizu] What a tough drive.
The sun's blindin'. It's in my eyes.
-It was such a nice trip.
-I know, right?
-What a nice trip.
-It was the best.
-It sure was.
-Yeah. It was over before I knew it.
It came and went all too fast.
-In the blink of an eye.
-It went by in a flash.
The trip went by fast,
but at the same time,
I felt as if I haven't
seen you guys in ages.
-Right, right.
-Yeah.
-It's a strange sensation.
-I know what you mean.
This trip came to a close.
We were divided up into three teams.
Because of it, I came to know
each member's personality,
or rather, their values.
I'm glad I got to go on a summer trip
with Noel's itinerary in the US.
-It was the best.
-It was so fun.
Remember when we all cried
our eyes out during the reunion?
Those tears came from
the deepest part of my heart.
-It was a good cry.
-Right.
I kept remembering moments from AGT.
I see.
It was similar to how emotions ran high
at the end of the first audition.
Right, right.
-It takes me back.
-I feel you.
It was unforgettable.
You only cry like that
a few times in your life.
-Exactly. It's a rare occasion.
-I haven't felt this way in a while.
We were brought to tears
because of our bond.
-Right.
-Looking back,
it felt as though we were still connected,
although we were miles apart.
-It's true.
-Maybe it was the tequila.
-But man, did we bawl like babies.
-Could've been the alcohol.
-Chaka, you were downing shots.
-I sure was.
There's one thing I can say for certain.
I'm grateful for all of you.
Sometimes, I get wrapped up in my head.
It's you who always pull me out
in those moments.
We support each other
with our differences.
That's rad.
-Says Chaka as he drives.
-Was that cool, or what?
You know, I can see the sun
reflecting off your sunglasses.
-It's making your face sparkle.
-How are you even able to see?
The sun is blinding.
-Wait, I'm getting a bit scared.
-Oh no, oh no.
Just lower the vanity mirror.
-That's ingenious. Nice!
-It's way too bright.
You said something profound.
What was it again?
-Don't forget it.
-Care to repeat it?
-[Noel] We keep going straight.
-On and on and on.
-[Noel] The road never ends.
-The road stretches on.
-What a beautiful view.
-[all exclaim]
-[whooping]
-Shall we travel around?
Guess we shall?
-Where should we go next?
-Yeah, what should our next trip be?
[♪ theme song piano version playing]
[♪ song stops]
[narrator, in English]
Los Angeles, California.
[in Japanese] Here we are.
Whoa!
Whoa, this brings me back!
-Isn't this it?
-Yes, this is the place. We're back!
-The height of this ceiling.
-It takes me back.
-This must be it.
-Yes. I remember this high ceiling.
[narrator] This is the very studio
where Travis Japan shot the cover
for their debut song, "JUST DANCE!"
Oh, wow.
Remember the changing ceiling lights?
We wore our TJ colors.
-This takes me back.
-Right?
-Shall we do "JUST DANCE!" once?
-Nice idea. I'm down!
-Let's do the chorus only.
-Dance the chorus only?
-We haven't been training, and I'm sore.
-The entire trip was an exercise.
We're only doing the chorus?
-Okay, I'm up for it.
-Where's my position?
Which way's the front of stage?
This direction?
Oh, over here.
-Shall we give it a go?
-Let's do it.
What if we start from…
Ready?
[band members singing]
Whoa.
That's "JUST DANCE!" for you!
-We did it!
-We killed it!
I'm feelin' it.
-That was great!
-I'm getting the feels.
Shall we snap a photo?
-Oh, let's do it.
-We came all this way, we might as well.
Where should we position the camera?
How about here, to start?
Nice.
-Do you remember how we lined up?
-How can I forget?
-Our usual position.
-Here for me?
You want to recreate the debut cover,
including the camera position. Right?
-It's coming back to me.
-Right here.
This feels right.
-I remember clearly. We're doing it right.
-This is our usual position.
That's right.
-This brings me back.
-Whoa!
-Oh, hold on. This is…
-[Shizu laughs]
-Oh man, you guys are killing it.
-Actually?
You're moving around. Ready for the photo?
Yep.
You sure? Are you mentally prepared
for the trip to end?
Our adventure won't end here.
Because, Machu…
Still on a journey.
Whoo!
Let's go!
Hey, hey, hey!
How do I put it… For some reason,
happy tears came out.
Maybe it's…
because of the life lessons
I learned on this trip.
That's right. It was such an invaluable
learning experience.
As a Travis Japan member,
there will be moments
when the lessons I learned from this trip
will carry me forward.
The last ten days were
so fulfilling and worthwhile.
What can I say?
Now that I had this chance to expand
my knowledge on modern America…
-Why don't you take a seat?
-I want to board the Amtrak. The Amtrak…
-You're so considerate. Thank you.
-Thanks.
-Oh, you don't wanna sit?
-Oh, I'm happy to oblige.
-Thank you, I'll sit on the right half.
-You sure? Okay.
Yes, it'd be great to ride
the Amtrak again.
Next time, I'd like to plan an Amtrak trip
with a completely different route.
Maybe I'll invite the members
for this one too,
but we won't make plans to meet up.
We'll see if we run into each other
at one of the stops.
It'd be fun to plan a trip
where everything is up to luck.
I was happy we ended our trip here.
Try as we may to hold fast
to the dreams we started out with,
as the days turn into months and years,
we often find ourselves forgetting
what we once set out to do.
That's why we need to return to our roots.
This trip gave me the chance
to return to my old dreams.
Now, I can continue onwards with
this renewed determination in my heart.
I saw many aspects of Travis Japan's,
well, personality.
Really, I did.
It was filled with many happy moments.
We had a lot of them, and…
And when our memories
finally reach the fans, then…
Oh my gosh, so happy.
I want to continue making memories
with Travis Japan.
I hope we do!
I have some of the best memories
of my life thanks to this trip.
I've also wised up a bit too.
I had many firsts on this trip. I've never
hiked such a tall mountain before.
It was also my first time visiting Arches.
I didn't expect to encounter so much
wildlife either. We even saw jackrabbits.
It was great to witness
the majestic landscapes
after hiking with the band members.
Let's see. Well…
first and foremost…
it gave me appreciation for life.
This was my first trip
that truly felt like an adventure.
Yeah.
Never before have I been
on a trip like this.
Not only was it fun,
it left me with a thirst for adventures.
Oh, really?
-Yeah. I want to venture out…
-Will we go again?
-…and see many new sights.
-You're gonna turn around?
-Didn't you feel similarly?
-I did.
In ten days alone, we visited
so many interesting places.
It reminded me that we can take off
with nothing but ourselves.
It opened my eyes to the world.
-That's wonderful.
-Thanks.
What is it?
Stop turning around to look at me.
-What about you, Kaito?
-Me? Let's see.
Next time, I want to visit France
and learn the background
-of my favorite brand.
-Right, right.
Yes, I want to learn
the roots of my favorite fashion.
I want to go somewhere in France.
-What a nice idea.
-How's this?
-I don't mind it.
-What?
How fun… This trip taught me
how to enjoy traveling.
-You're right. You're right.
-Now, the possibilities are endless.
Travis Japan's adventure continues on.
Can we keep moving forward with everyone?
Agreed!
[cheering]
-Thanks, guys!
-It was the best trip ever!
[Noel] We found our roots
in this summer vacation.
Translated by Megumi Hunter